Finding Aid for the Ralph Edwards Productions Production Records PASC.0336
UCLA Library Special Collections
- This is Your Life, 1952-1987; Series 1.
  - Research Material, Scripts and Sound Recordings, Subseries 1.
    - Laura Stone Marr, 1952 October 1 (Box 236)
      Subject is a pioneer woman and mother of Milburn Stone ('Doc' of "Gunsmoke.")
    - Gary Marshall, 1984 April 12 (Box 61)
      Subject is a television producer. Includes: script; research notes. Guests include: Jerry Belson, favorite collaborator ("The Odd Couple") and friend; writer, producer; Ron Howard, actor; Milt Josefsberg, famous TV writer; Jack Klugman, actor; Penny Marshall, actress.
    - Mary Martin, 1972 August 9 (Box 61)
      Subject is a film and stage star. Includes: script; research notes. Guests include: Janet Gaynor, Academy Award winning actress (winner of first "Best Actress" Oscar); widow of costume designer Adrian, wife of TIYL producer Paul Gregory; Richard Halliday, husband and manager.
    - Mary Ann, 1954 June 2 (Box 61)
      Subject is a recovering narcotics addict. Includes: script; research notes.
    - Mike Masaoka, 1956 January 2 (Box 61)
      Subject is a Nisei veteran. includes: script; research notes.
    - Clarinda Mason, 1954 December 22 (Box 61)
      Subject "adopted" 300 servicemen during World War II. Includes: script; research notes.
    - Matthews, Stanley, 1955 July 29 (Box 302)
      Script for the first broadcast of the English series.
    - Hans Mauch, 1960 October 2 (Box 61)
      Subject is an Ice Follies skating star: "Frack" of "Frick and Frack." Includes: script; research notes. Guests include: Werner "Frick" Groebli; David Jenkins, champion figure skater, Olympic gold medalist; Oscar Johnson, co-owner of the "Ice Follies"; Dr. James Koch, President of the International Figure Skating Union; Dr. Carl Pearson, Head of the Arthritic Clinic at UCLA Medical Center; Eddie Shipstad and Roy Shipstad, co-owners of "Ice Follies".
    - Ray May, 1971 January 28 (Box 61)
      Subject is a football star. Includes: script; research notes. Guests include: Roy Jefferson, football player, teammate, roommate on Baltimore Colts; John McKay, his football coach at USC; Jim Pendleton, his football coach at Los Angeles High School.
    - Ray May, 1971 January 28 (Box 236)
      Subject is a football star.
    - John McCallum, 1976 March 30 (Box 220)
    - Charlie McCarthy, 1950 March 1-8; streaming audio (Box 218)
      Subject is a radio star (voiced by Edgar Bergen). Includes: script, research notes, audio. Guests include: Edgar Bergen, ventriloquist, stage, screen and radio star; Velma Wayne, actress, built the Howdy Doody puppet then seen on TV; W. C. Fields (film clip played); Ken Murray, actor, comedian; star and producer of "Blackouts"; Maureen O'Sullivan, actress.
    - Jim McClain, 1952 November 26 (Box 61)
      The subject is a radio personality who became an Episcopal Minister. Includes: script; research notes. Guests include: Tol Ware Avery, actor; Perry Dickey, former director of the "Dr. I.Q." show; Dale Evans, Western star.
    - Felix McCool, 1958 April 2 (Box 61)
    - Tim McCoy, 1958 November 5 (Box 62)
      Subject is a Western star. Includes: script; research notes. Guests include: Paul Benton, President of the Civil War Round Table of Southern California; Iron Eyes Cody, Native American actor; Al Jennings, traveled with subject during the Ringling Bros. days; William Shakespeare, Arapahoe Indian.
    - Joel McCrea, 1972 September 19 (Box 62)
      Subject is a film star. Includes: script; research notes. Guests include: Chairman of the Board of Directors, National Cowboy Hall of Fame; Gene Autry, cowboy star; fellow Cowboy Hall of Fame honoree and member of the Board of Directors; Gov. David Hall, Governor of Oklahoma; Dorothy Mackaill, actress; Col. Tim McCoy, old time cowboy actor; Frances Dee, wife, actress; Gov. Ronald Reagan, Governor of California, friend, "fellow rancher"; William Wellman, film director.
    - Mary Barbara McDonough, 1949 October 12; streaming audio (Box 218)
      Subject is a 19 year old auditioning for the Ice Follies. Includes: script, research notes, audio.
    - Alice Middleton McDougall, 1956 June 13 (Box 62)
      Subject is a Lusitania survivor. Includes: script; research notes. Guests include: Milton Berle, comedian; Col. John D. Craig, author, deep sea diver, producer of TV's "Kingdom of the Sea"; Captain John I. Lewis, was Third Navigation Officer on the Lusitania in 1915; Eugene Williams, past president of the L.A. Adventurers Club.
    - Alice Middleton McDougall, 1956 June 13 (Box 236)
      Subject is a Lusitania survivor.
    - Terry McGee, 1984 February 6 (Box 62)
      The subject has had a lifetime struggle to become a doctor. Includes: script; research notes. Guests include: Kelly Greer, model; the Lennon Sisters (Janet Lennon, Kathy Lennon and Peggy Lennon); Tom Trbovich, producer and director; Vanna White, model.
    - Eva McGown, 1953 April 22 (Box 62)
      Subject is a humanitarian from Fairbanks, Alaska. Includes: script; research notes. Guests include: Jack McElroy, host of "Breakfast in Hollywood" radio show.
    - Jimmy McHugh, 1952 October 8 (Box 62)
      Subject is a song writer. Includes: script; research notes. Guests include: Max Baer, former world heavyweight champion boxer; Florence Chadwick, champion swimmer; Bob Crosby, singer; Nick Fatool, drummer in Bob Crosby's jazz band "The Bob Cats"; Morty Korb, bass player in Bob Crosby's jazz band "The Bob Cats"; Matty Matlock, clarinet player in Bob Crosby's jazz band "The Bob Cats"; Eddie Miller, saxophone player in Bob Crosby's jazz band "The Bob Cats"; Gertrude Niessen, singer and actress; Louella Parsons, Hollywood gossip columnist; Charlie Teagarden, trumpet player in Bob Crosby's jazz band "The Bob Cats"; Jack Teagarden, trombone player in Bob Crosby's jazz band "The Bob Cats"; Stan Wrightsman, band member in Bob Crosby's jazz band "The Bob Cats".
    - Sir Arthur McIlveen, 1977 May 27 (Box 220)
    - Heather McKay, 1977 April 29 (Box 220)
    - Victor McLaglen, 1953 October 28 (Box 62)
      Subject is a film star. Includes: script; research notes. Guests include: Edmund Lowe, actor.
    - Audrie and Neil McLeod, 1975 December 5 (Box 220)
    - Mary McLeod Bethune, 1949 March 15 (Box 217)
      script; research notes. Guests include: Eleanor Roosevelt, via transcription - former First Lady (widow of FDR, in whose administration Bethune served), good friend.
      Subject is an educator.
    - Don McNeill, 1960 January 20 (Box 62)
      Subject is a radio personality. Includes: script; research notes. Guests include: Fran Allison, radio actress ("Kukla, Fran and Ollie"), regular on "Breakfast Club"; Eddie Ballantine, "Breakfast Club" music director; Ralph Bergsten, Vice President and General Manager of Don McNeill Enterprises; Anita Bryant, "Breakfast Club" vocalist; Sam Cowling, "Breakfast Club" comic; Eddy McKean, "Breakfast Club" announcer; Dennis Morgan, actor; Dick Noel, "Breakfast Club" vocalist; Cliff Petersen, "Breakfast Club" radio producer; Bill Thompson, radio star; got his start on the "Breakfast Club".
    - John Meillon, 1977 June 14 (Box 220)
    - Lauritz Melchior, 1958 December 10 (Box 62)
      Subject is an operatic tenor. Includes: script; research notes. Guests include: William Chapman, opera singer; Kenneth Hansen, chef and owner of the Scandia Restaurant in Los Angeles; Lotte Lehmann, opera singer; Maria "Kleinchen" (Mrs. Lauritz) Melchior, wife, former European film star; Joseph Pasternak, MGM producer.
    - Lauritz Melchior, 1958 December 10 (Box 236)
      Subject is an operatic tenor.
    - Rachel Mellinger, 1953 November 18 (Box 62)
    - Ethel Merman, 1971 April 29 (Box 62)
      Includes: script; research notes. Subject is a film and stage star. Guests include: Merv Griffin, TV talk show host; Jerry Herman, composer of "Hello, Dolly"; Bob Hope (via videotape) co-starred with her and Durante on Broadway in "Red, Hot and Blue"; Russell Nype, actress; Temple Texas, former actress and press agent; Benay Venuta, actress.
    - Darlene Miller, 1956 October 31 (Box 62)
      Includes: script; research notes. Subject is one of a family of orphaned farm children who struggled to remain together as a family.
    - Commander Hugh Barr Miller, Jr., 1957 January 30 (Box 62)
      World War II survival story. Includes script and research notes.
    - Commander Hugh Barr Miller, Jr., 1957 January 30 (Box 236)
      World War II survival story.
      Host: Ronald Reagan. Annotated script.
    - Kathy Miller, 1984 April 26 (Box 62)
      Includes: script; research notes. Success story of an accident victim. Guests include: Bruce Jenner, 1976 Olympic Decathlon gold medalist; Larry Miller, father, former professional baseball player with Dodgers, Mets, Giants; Dr. Art Mollen, sports doctor, syndicated newspaper columnist; Jerry Weiss, TIYL director.
    - Keith Miller, 1977 March 12 (Box 220)
    - Marion Miller, 1956 March 28 (Box 62)
      Includes:script; research notes. Subject is an FBI Communist investigator.
    - Marion Miller, 1956 March 28 (Box 236)
      Subject is an FBI Communist investigator.
    - Florence Milligan, 1976 May 31; script; research notes (Box 220)
    - Billy Mills, 1984 January 17 (Box 62)
      Subject is an Olympic gold medalist. Includes script and research notes. Guests include: Robby Benson, actor, star of movie "Running Brave", friend - reads telegram from Pres. Reagan; Ira Englander, producer of movie "Running Brave".
    - Robert Mitchell, 1949 December 21; streaming audio (Box 218)
      script, research notes, audio. Subject is the founder of the Mitchell Boys Choir. Guests include: Mitchell Choir Boys; Eddie Cantor, singer; Marian Goldwyn, campaign spokesperson for the National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis.
    - Harry Momita, 1958 May 21 (Box 62)
      Subject is a Japanese immigrant with unwavering devotion to the United States. Includes script and research notes. Guests include: Franklin Garrett, Calipatria, CA City Council member; Frank Kuwahara, neighbor in wartime relocation camp; Sam Packwood, Superintendent of schools in El Centro, CA; Mayor Ed Rademaker, Mayor of Calipatria, CA.
    - Archie Moore, 1959 October 14 (Box 62)
      Subject is a World Light-Heavyweight champion. Includes script and research notes. Guests include: George Davis, Los Angeles Herald writer; Mel Durslag, Los Angeles Examiner writer; Hiawatha Gray, one of subject's trainers; Larry Gross, agent; Rocky Marciano, former world heavyweight champion; Sid Ziff, Los Angeles Mirror writer; Paul Zimmerman, Los Angeles Times writer.
    - Tom Moore, 1954 June 9 (Box 62)
      Subject is a pioneer film star. Includes script and research notes. Guests include: Robert Ellis, screenwriter; Glenn Ford, actor; Marguerite Courtout (Mrs. Raymond) McKee, leading lady in subject's early films (stage name: Marguerite Courtout); Matt Moore, actor.
    - Thelma Morgan, 1954 March 3 (Box 62)
      Subject is a champion dog breeder. Includes script and research notes. Guests include: Bert Heath, Dog Editor, Los Angeles Times.
    - Greg Morris, 1972 July 17 (Box 62)
      Subject is a television star. Includes a script and research notes. Guests include: Bob Cousey, coach of the Kansas City/Omaha Kings, former basketball star with the Boston Celtics; Peter Graves, actor; Gene Keene, director; Jack Kelly, Deputy Regional Director of the Bureau of Narcotics and Dangerous Drugs; Peter Lupus, actor; Hank Roberts, agent; Herb Solow, former Head of Production for Desilu Studios - made the decision to produce the "Mission, Impossible" series; David Van Putten, choir director, Washington High School, L.A..
    - Athol Mulley, 1977 February 18; script; research notes (Box 220)
    - Audi Murphy, 1949 March 8; streaming audio (Box 218)
      script, research notes, audio. Subject is the most decorated soldier of World War II. Guests include: Ann Blyth, via remote from the Central Market, 5200 Lankershim Blvd., North Hollywood (after Murphy "Life") - actress, movie star; Wanda Hendrix, wife, actress; Charles Lyon, via remote from the Central Market, 5200 Lankershim Blvd., North Hollywood (after Murphy "Life"); Martha Scott, actress; Freddie Slack, musician, bandleader; Robert Stack, actor.
    - Ken Murray, 1960 May 18 (Box 62)
      Subject is a stage, screen and television comedian. Includes script and research notes. Guests include: Edgar Bergen, ventriloquist, actor; vaudeville, radio star; Bud Carlell, vaudeville and stage star; Laurie (Mrs. Robert Gross) Anders, actress; Arthur Lake, actor, best known as "Dagwood"; Jack Oakie, actor; Mayor Norris Poulson, Mayor of Los Angeles; Penny Singleton, actress, best known as "Blondie"; Harry Von Zell, radio announcer; Marie Wilson, actress.
    - Ken Murray, 1960 May 18 (Box 236)
      Subject is a stage, screen and television comedian.
    - Stan Musial, 1970 December 8; script; research notes (Box 62)
      Subject is a baseball player. Includes script and research notes. Guests include: Bob "Doc" Bauman, long time trainer of the St. Louis Cardinals; Al Campanis, baseball executive, Dodgers front office; Bowie Kuhn, baseball commissioner; Jim Maloney, baseball player, pitcher with Cincinnati Reds; Red Schoendienst, former baseball player, friend, roommate and teammate; now manager of the St. Louis Cardinals; Truett Banks "Rip" Sewell, former baseball player, friend, roommate and teammate; now manager of the St. Louis Cardinals; Enos Slaughter, former baseball player, friend and teammate on St. Louis Cardinals; Johnny Van De Meer, former baseball player (pitcher for the Cincinnati Reds); Ollie Vanek, former manager of St. Louis Cardinals' Monessa, PA minor league baseball team, signed subject to play professional baseball.
    - Betty Muzyczuk, 1977 May 17; script; research notes (Box 220)
    - Harry and Allison Neal, 1959 January 14 (Box 62)
      Subjects are concert pianists travelling by bus. Includes script and research notes. Guests include: Marjorie Lawrence, opera and concert star; William Primrose, concert violinist.
    - Jack Neary, 1976 October 19; script; research notes (Box 220)
    - Ada Nelligan, 1948 November 23; streaming audio (Box 62)
      script (photocopy),audio. Subject is a New York theatrical wardrobe mistress. Guests include: Joan Crawford, actress; Don DeFore, actor; Maurice Evans, Shakespearian actor, hired her as his company's wardrobe mistress 1936-1942; Al Jolson, entertainer (singer, actor, movie star); John Lund, actor; Barbara Stanwyck, actress; Irene Tedrow, actress; Rhys Williams, actor.
    - Ada Nelligan, 1948 November 23 (Box 218)
      Subject is a New York theatrical wardrobe mistress. Includes script and research notes.
    - Ralph G. Neppel, 1949 February 8; streaming audio (Box 218)
      script, audio. Subject is a disabled 25 year old Iowa farmer and Congressional Honor recipient.
    - Ralph G. Neppel, 1949 February 8; streaming audio (Box 236)
      script, audio. Subject is a disabled 25 year old Iowa
    - Dorothy and J.B. Nethercutt, 1979 September 11; script; research notes (Box 235)
    - Dr. Kate Pelham Newcomb, 1954 March 17 (Box 62)
      Subject is the Northwoods Wisconsin country doctor Includes script and research notes.
    - Dr. Kate Pelham Newcomb, 1954 March 17 (Box 236)
    - Dr. Kate Pelham Newcomb, 1954 March 17 (Box 236)
      Subject is the Northwoods Wisconsin country doctor.
      Annotated script. (2 copies)
    - Red Nichols, 1956 October 3 (Box 62)
      Subject is a band leader. Includes script and research notes. Guests include: Victor Angle, drummer; Jimmy Dorsey, bandleader, musician (sax and clarinet); Phil Harris, musician; David Klein, music contractor; Miff Mole, trombonist; Arthur Schutt, pianist; Charlie Teagarden, trumpet player; Jack Teagarden, trombonist.
    - Frances Nickmann, 1954 June 16 (Box 63)
      Subject is a Chicago Policewoman. Includes script and research notes.
    - Dr. Mungai Njoroge, 1959 March 18 (Box 63)
      Subject is an African doctor. Includes script and research notes.
    - Dr. Mungai Njoroge, 1959 March 18 (Box 236)
    - Ted Noffs, 1975 November 7; script; research notes (Box 220)
    - Kathleen Norris, 1955 October 12; script; research notes (Box 63)
      Subject is an author and humanitarian. Includes script and research notes.
    - Bill Northam, 1976 May 27; script; research notes (Box 220)
    - Dr. Max Nussbaum, 1959 April 22 (Box 63)
      Subject is a German Rabbi who resisted the Nazis. Includes script and research notes. Guests include: Steve Broidy, head of Allied Artists Pictures.
    - Dr. David D. Oak, 1949 February 22; streaming audio (Box 218)
      script, audio. Subject is an Indiana country doctor.
    - Lieutenant James Obenauf, 1959 June 3; script; research notes (Box 222)
    - Colonel Serge Obolensky, 1959 March 11 (Box 222)
      Subject is a Russian expatriate and OSS officer. Includes script and research notes. Guests include: Michael Arens, cellist; Dimitri Tiomkin, composer; Cobina Wright, columnist.
    - Pat O'Brien, 1953 June 10 (Box 63)
      Subject is a film star. Includes script and research notes. Guests include: Johnny Mack Brown, actor, movie star, former college football great; Wally Ford, actor; Jimmy Gleason, actor, director, producer; Allen Jenkins, actor; Mary Brian (Mrs. George) Tomasini, actress; Fay Wray, actress.
    - Pat O'Brien, 1953 June 10 (Box 236)
    - Maureen O'Hara, 1957 March 27 (Box 63)
      Subject is a film star. Includes script and research notes. Subject is being interviewed in the Pantages Theatre lobby at Academy Awards ceremony. Guests include: John Ford, film director; James Fox, brother, actor; Charles Laughton, film producer; Eric Pommer, film producer; Joe Williams, Irish soccer great; with team "Shamrock Rovers".
    - Johnny O'Keefe, 1975 October 1; script; research notes (Box 220)
    - Ole Olsen, 1961 January 25 (Box 222)
      Subject is a comedian. Includes script and research notes. Guests include: Milton Berle, comedian, TV personality; Ray Evans, Academy Award winning songwriter (lyricist), partner of Jay Livingston; Jay Livingston, Academy Award winning songwriter (composer).
    - Ole Olsen, 1961 February 5 (Box 236)
      Subject is a comedian.
    - Thomas Orley, 1956 December 26 (Box 222)
      Subject is a Hungarian refugee. Includes script and research notes.
    - Carey Orr, 1961 May 11 (Box 222)
      Subject is a cartoonist. Includes script and research notes. Guests include: Karl Hubenthal, editorial cartoonist for the Los Angeles Examiner newspaper; Tom Little, Nashville political cartoonist; Shaw McCutcheon, Spokane political cartoonist (son of famed political cartoonist John T. McCutcheon); Joe Parrish, cartoonist; Bruce Russell, editorial cartoonist for the Los Angeles Times newspaper.
    - Major Peter Ortiz, 1949 November 9; streaming audio (Box 218)
      script, audio. Subject is an OSS Operative in World War II Europe.
    - Helen Ostrowski, 1955 January 5 (Box 222)
      Subject is a Russian displaced person and American citizen. Includes script and research notes.
    - Jesse Owens, 1960 April 27 (Box 222)
      Subject is an Olympic gold medalist. Includes script and research notes. Guests include: Dave Albritton, Olympic teammate (silver medal in high jump in 1936);Ralph Metcalf, 1936 Olympic relay teammate (gold medalist); Rev. Robert "Bob" Richards, Olympic athlete; Lawrence Snyder, head coach of the 1960 U.S. Olympic men's track and field team; Frank Wykoff, 1936 Olympic relay teammate (gold medalist) - from Los Angeles, CA.
    - Jesse Owens, 1960 April 27 (Box 236)
      Subject is an Olympic gold medalist.
    - LeRoy "Satchel" Paige, 1971 October 22 (Box 222)
      Subject is a baseball legend. Includes script and research notes. Guests include: Newt Allen, former Negro League baseball player, 2nd baseman, teammate on the Kansas City Monarchs; Chester Arnold, former Negro League baseball player, pitcher, teammate on the Chattanooga Black Lookouts in 1926; Vida Blue, baseball player, pitcher with Oakland A's; Lou Boudreau, player-manager of the Cleveland Indians, Hall of Famer, now announcer for the Chicago Cubs; subject's first major league manager; Frank Duncan, former Negro League baseball player, catcher; teammate for 15 years on the Kansas City Monarchs; William Lowe, former Negro League baseball player, 3rd baseman, teammate on the Chattanooga Black Lookouts; Ted Page, former Negro League baseball player, outfielder, teammate on the Pittsburgh Crawfords in 1932.
    - Dr. Martin Palmer, 1960 January 13 (Box 222)
      Subject is a pioneer speech pathologist. Includes script and research notes. Guests include: Adolphe Menjou, actor; Jane Wyman, actress.
    - Peter Palmer, 1961 February 7 (Box 222)
      Subject is a film star. Includes script and research notes. Guests include: Al Capp, cartoonist, creator of "Li'l Abner"; George Chandler, President of Screen Actor's Guild; Melvin Frank, "Li'l Abner" producer; Stan Greeson, personal manager; Norman Panama, "Li'l Abner" producer.
    - Peter Palmer, 1961 February 12 (Box 236)
    - Brad Parks, 1984 February 27 (Box 222)
      Subject is a paraplegic who pioneered wheelchair tennis. Includes script and research notes. Guests include: Vic Braden, famous tennis coach; Beau Bridges, actor; Rosco Tanner, one of the all-time great tennis players.
    - Freddie Parsons, 1977 July 8; script; research notes (Box 220)
    - Tony Pastor, 1960 June 8 (Box 222)
      Subject is a musician/singer. Includes script and research notes. Guests include: Irving Aaronson, former bandleader; Les Burness, road manager and pianist; Lee Castle, bandleader (leads Dorsey Brothers Band) and trumpet player; Jerry Gray, bandleader and arranger; Worthy Hills, former bandleader and club owner; Buddy Morrow, bandleader and trombone player.
    - Vic Patrick, 1977 April 6; script; research notes (Box 220)
    - Belden Paulson, 1958 March 5 (Box 222)
      Subject formed an organization to assist Italian refugees. Includes script and research notes. Guests include: Hope Lange, actress; Don Murray, actor; James Read, U. N. Deputy High Commissioner for Refugees.
    - Dr. Norman Vincent Peale, 1954 November 17 (Box 222)
      Subject is a minister and writer. Includes script and research notes. Guests include: Carl Erskine, Brooklyn Dodgers pitcher; Dale Evans, Western actress and singer.
    - Dr. Norman Vincent Peale, 1954 November 17 (Box 236)
      Subject is a minister and writer.
    - Minnie Pearl, 1957 May 1 (Box 222)
      Subject is a Grand Old Opry star. Includes script and research notes. Guests include: Eddy Arnold, country singer; Pee Wee King, musician, former Grand Ole Opry star; Ted Switzer, with NBC publicity department; Claude Thompson, NBC's head make-up man.
    - Minnie Pearl, 1957 May 1 (Box 236)
      Subject is a Grand Old Opry star.
    - Corney Pearson, 1953 May 13 (Box 222)
      Subject is a grocery clerk. Includes script and research notes. Guests include: Spring Byington, actress; J. C. Penney, owner of company for which she once worked.
    - Theodore Augustus Penland, 1949 November 30 (Box 218)
      Subject is a Civil War veteran. Includes script and research notes. Guests include: Marian Goldwyn, campaign spokesperson for the National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis; Alfred E. Lyon, Chairman of the Board of Directors of Philip Morris; Carlos Romulo, President of the U.N. General Assembly.
    - Charles H. Percy, 1950 January 18; streaming audio (Box 218)
      script, research notes, audio. Subject is Man of the Year.
    - Jill Perryman, 1976 July 19; script; research notes (Box 220)
    - Clare Phillips, 1950 March 15; streaming audio (Box 218)
      script, audio. Subject is a woman spy in World War II Philippines.
    - Dr. Bob Pierce, 1961 March 29 (Box 222)